netdna-storage.com 2017-06-18

# Privacy Policy | netDNA Storage

For the purposes of this Agreement, the following definitions apply and any undefined terms have the meaning ascribed to them in the context in which they are used in this Agreement:

### **A. Personally-Identifiable Information:**

netDNA Storage typically receives specific data about its website visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information, purchase or enroll for services, open a customer support inquiry ticket, provide resume information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these activities require that you give us information, such as when you make a purchase, use a credit card to pay for services, submit your resume, or request certain types of information. When you provide personally-identifiable information to netDNA Storage through one of our websites, it will be used to fulfill your specific request. In most cases, you will be given the opportunity to select whether you do, or do not, want netDNA Storage to use this information for additional purposes.

netDNA Storage will not, however, sell or trade your personally-identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so, or in the case of imminent physical harm to the visitor or others. On those netDNA Storage sites where you may provide netDNA Storage with credit card or other ordering information via the web, netDNA Storage protects and secures this information by employing commercially customary web-based security and encryption protocols, examples of which include Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and Secure Electronic Transaction (SET). 

#### **Targeted Advertisements**

Absent any instructions from you, netDNA Storage may use information you provide to inform you about additional services and products offered by the netDNA Storage family of companies, netDNA Storage venture companies, netDNA Storage authorized agents, and other goods and services providers with whom netDNA Storage has relationships and whose offerings might be of interest to you.

#### **Supplementation of Information**

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personally identifiable information you submit to us with information from third party sources (e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service). We do this to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our products and services to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

#### **Opt-out**

netDNA Storage customers control how and when we contact you by logging into the [Account](http://netdna-storage.com/auth/login) and changing your preferences. netDNA Storage reserves the right, in its discretion, to send you bulletins and other important information about your netDNA Storage services. If you are not a netDNA Storage customer and wish not to be emailed about our services, please click the unsubscribe link in the email you have received.

### **B. Non Personally-Identifiable (Generic) Information:**

In general, netDNA Storage gathers some generic information automatically. Generic information does not reveal the identity of the visitor. It usually includes information about the Internet address assigned to your computer, the number and frequency of visitors, and the netDNA Storage sites visited. netDNA Storage gathers this information for the limited purpose of determining customer service and website needs. We accomplish this by using certain technologies, including "cookies" (a technology that can be used to provide the visitor with tailored information about netDNA Storage services). netDNA Storage does not combine information collected in this way with any personally-identifiable information.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and you can refuse it; this may however reduce functionality of certain website features such as the order system and the [Account](http://netdna-storage.com/auth/login).

### **C. Your netDNA Storage hosted website, server, bulletin boards, forum, Third-Party Sites:**

Information that you disclose in a public space, including on any blog, bulletin board, chat room, or website netDNA Storage may host for you as part of your netDNA Storage services, is available to anyone else who visits that space. netDNA Storage cannot safeguard any information you disclose in these locations. Additionally, netDNA Storage websites contain links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to netDNA Storage. netDNA Storage cannot protect any information you may disclose in these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.

On those sites where you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or the like, netDNA Storage will treat that portion of the information as non-confidential and nonproprietary and, except as otherwise expressed in this privacy statement, netDNA Storage assumes no obligation to protect such information from disclosure.

### **D. Exceptions and Limitations:**

Notwithstanding the foregoing and in compliance with applicable laws, netDNA Storage (i) cooperates fully with state, local, and federal officials in any investigation relating to any content (including personal or private electronic communications transmitted to netDNA Storage) or purported unlawful activities of any user of the Service, and (ii) takes reasonable measures to protect its proprietary rights. For the limited purposes of accomplishing such cooperation and measures and in compliance with applicable laws, netDNA Storage may be required to disclose personally identifiable information. In addition, netDNA Storage may elect to monitor the areas of communication of any kind (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate netDNA Storage; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of netDNA Storage or others. In connection with the potential sale or transfer of any of its interest in mediatemple.net, and ac.mediatemple.net and other sites owned by the company, netDNA Storage reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including, but not limited to name, address information, and other information you provided to netDNA Storage) to a third party that (i) concentrates its business in communication products or services; (ii) agrees to be netDNA Storage's successor in interest with regard to the maintenance and protection of information collected and maintained by netDNA Storage; and (iii) agrees to the obligations of this policy statement.

### **E. Transfer of Data Abroad:**

If you are visiting this site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers.
